<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<NewsFeed>
  <Entry id="modular-consoles-migration" type="migration_needed" severity="critical" heading="Modular Consoles – Action Required">
    <short_description>- a letter from WIKUS</short_description>
    <long_description>[h1]The original Modular Consoles Mod is no longer maintained - What happened?[/h1]
Tom, the original developer of [b]Modular Consoles[/b], has been unreachable for some time. I don't know the details, and I wish him well - but in his absence, the mod has broken on recent game versions and there is no way for me to push fixes to Tom's Workshop entry.

[h1]What are we doing about it?[/h1]
      
I have taken over maintenance of the mod under my own Workshop page. The new version is up to date, actively maintained, and a drop-in replacement for our original.

Clicking [b]Migrate[/b] below will automatically unsubscribe you from the old entry and subscribe you to the maintained version on my (WIKUS's) workshop. [b]Your saves are safe.[/b]

[h1]A note from me[/h1]
I'm sorry you're seeing this at all — this isn't how any of us wanted things to go. Tom helpted me built something great, and we're just trying to make sure it keeps working for everyone.

— [b]Wikus with a little help from JacksonTheMaster, Aproposmath and Inaki [/b]

[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3452651592]View the maintained Workshop page[/url]</long_description>
    <Trigger match_type="workshop_id" workshop_id="3505169479" />
    <Actions>
      <Primary label="Migrate Mod" action="workshop_mod_install" workshop_id="3452651592" />
      <Secondary label="Open Workshop Page" action="open_url" url="https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3452651592" />
    </Actions>
  </Entry>
  <Entry id="libconstruct-migration" type="migration_needed" severity="critical" heading="LibConstruct – Action Required">
    <short_description> - migrate no  w</short_description>
    <long_description>[h1]The original LibConstruct Mod is no longer maintained[/h1]
      But wait - what even is LibConstruct?
[b]LibConstruct[/b] is a shared library that [b]Modular Consoles[/b] and some other mods depends on. It was authored by Tom_is_unlucky, who has been unreachable for some time. We don't know the details, and we wish him well - but in his absence, the mod has broken on recent game versions and there is no way for us to push fixes to his Workshop entry.

[h1]What are we doing about it?[/h1]
Just like Modular Consoles, We've published a maintained version under WIKUS's Workshop page. Clicking [b]Migrate[/b] will unsubscribe you from the old entry and subscribe you to the working one automatically.

— [b]Wikus with a little help from JacksonTheMaster, Aproposmath and Inaki [/b]

[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3328065049]View the maintained Workshop page[/url]</long_description>
    <Trigger match_type="workshop_id" workshop_id="3505115682" />
    <Actions>
      <Primary label="Migrate Mod" action="workshop_mod_install" workshop_id="3328065049" />
      <Secondary label="Open Workshop Page" action="open_url" url="https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3328065049" />
    </Actions>
  </Entry>
</NewsFeed>
